That a person becomes or deteriorates on the basis of feelings, work
done with good feelings helps a common
man to move ahead in life,
people working with good feelings always move ahead, it is good feelings that
help to touch the heights in life,
Hello friends, I Mahadev
welcome you and here we are going to see the
importance of good feelings,
before starting the video, if you are new to the channel, then do
not forget to subscribe to the channel,
if you like this video, then do
not forget to like the video and those who want to
know about the internet,
subscribe to the designated channel, so
friends, let's
start today's video,
insurance or illness always
works on the basis of good feelings, which is
called at most gufit in English,
it works with utmost trust from both the sides, both the insurance company and the
person taking the insurance, at the
time of taking the insurance and giving the insurance, it
becomes a very responsible job to tell the material facts between the two, if
anyone refers someone to the insurance company, then he
is subscribed to it, similarly, if you go to take a policy, then it is
very important for you too to
subscribe to it, about yourself  I
thank you for disclosing all the facts to the insurance company
and the insurance company which is offering you the policy also
explains all the terms and conditions of the policy to you very well. This is a display of
trust or good intentions towards both of them.
If material facts are not disclosed
while taking insurance or when the insurance companies
offer insurance, then there is a
high possibility of problems in the future.
If someone takes material facts due to not doing so, then there
may be difficulty in making a claim. If the person taking the insurance company
forgets to give any material information about himself or about the subscriber
or does
not give any information, then when the claim
comes, the insurance company may
not even pay the policy at the time of claim, so there are
chances of it getting disputed in the future.
We can understand the importance of good intentions with a small
example. Suppose
a person named Rohit wants to buy a health insurance
policy, then he does
not bother about some things
or he does not know about the policy
producer.  If he does not do it, then going
forward, after subscribing,
if
after 14 years of obscure, if there is a disease, if
before voting for high BP, before which
he is not covered, if
Rohit's claim comes, then the
company will be unable to pay Rohit's claim or else
Rohit's claim may get activated
because Rohit did
not inform the company about the hybrid that he consumed, otherwise
his gland may also get rejected due to this,
once the claim gets rejected, then
Rohit will have to pay his plan from his own pocket with his own money,
so if
he reduces this in advance, then the company would have
known and the company would have told him in advance
that whatever you are suffering from,
whatever the timeline is, that time will be only after lunch, then there may be a
dispute in future or there may be a
problem in future,
problem cannot arise,
good feeling in insurance or at most difficult,
how can this principle work, in this small
video we have learned a very big,
very basic principle from this and such
For many such knowledgeable videos, keep watching your
channel Insurance Guruji and
share your channel with all your friends who want information about insurance. If
you have not yet subscribed to the channel,
please subscribe to the channel and
press the bell icon and click on all so that
you get information about upcoming videos in advance
and you can watch the video and
gain knowledge about insurance and health insurance. Thank you
[Sangeet]